Drew Cook

621 South Lincoln St. #310 • Denver, CO • 80209
CELL (225) 328-1000 • E-MAIL drewcook29@gmail.com

SUMMARY

An entry-level developer, and an avid musician, excited to pursue a career in front-end web development. I have spent the last twelve years playing instruments and learning the craft, and in doing so developed a love for technology. Interestingly enough, making music and writing code share similar qualities. Both require a strong sense of creativity, an aptitude for design, and a knack for problem solving. As a developer, I can utilize these strengths when approaching new projects, designing web pages and programs, and improving the user experience. I look forward to helping customers bring their ideas to life, and will be an integral part in helping my employer grow and succeed.

EDUCATION

SeedPaths - Denver,

Aug 2014 - Oct 2014

- SeedPaths is an 8-week intensive software and professional development boot camp.
 Fundamental software development skills focused on .NET technologies
- Professional skills in areas of team collaboration, conflict management, and professional communication

Louisiana State University - Baton Rouge, LA

Aug 2008 - May 2011

Landscape Architecture & Communication Studies

SKILLS

Certifications: Certified Scrum Master

Software Development: .Net, HTML5, CSS3, C#, MVC4, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL **Musicianship:** Apple Logic Pro, Drums and Percussion, Guitar, Mandolin, Bass

EXPERIENCE

Multiband Inc. - Scott, LA

Technician, Jan 2012 - Aug 2013

- Provided satellite TV services to residential homes serving 60-80 customers per month
- Designed an individualized plan for every home served to accommodate the building layout and yielded best reception possible while meeting industry standards and code
- Top performer within my team and attained high customer satisfaction ratings and low service on service calls every month

GrisGris - New Orleans, LA

Drummer, Oct 2010 – Jan 2012

- Louisiana-based funk/rock fusion band playing around the New Orleans and Greater Baton Rouge areas
- Collaborated in a team environment presenting creative musical ideas
- Promoted upcoming shows through marketing and social media